- name your channel ad stop with such as
pass material nasha Nagaraj the way my
Caravaggio Maria cutoff parodied
Borowski yon Edisto at the Palmer guy at
one store savonia - Guevara
meditate su problema militancy fix
about you okay and we're broadcasting
from Diamond Mountain University this is
the I think it's the largest retreat
center in United States versus amakuni
retreat center sitting on the start of
American we tried to find the most empty
place in America tiniest of American so
we have thirty beautiful meditation
cabins receiveth to make up to meet at
sea in the desert in Arizona whose thing
about Sonya and in the desert you have
to have a cowboy hat what is done in
Austin I see the Cowboys car shop course
Napa and you gotta have cowboy boots
those live with but Cena kicking voice
kill
so we're hoping all the Cowboys in
Arizona we meditate with our boots on
Sam wake up boy what is only material
but simcha and with our cowboy hats you
boys could level it's good if you have a
cowgirl is Cowboys crazy over stuff
all right so we're gonna talk about
typical problems in meditation the
problem of five problems in meditation
and you know you expect if there are
five problems and and we're gonna go for
one hour I'm so if you if there are five
classical problems in meditation yes yes
problem minutes in everybody gets these
five promise it doesn't matter what
country you live in every human mind
that meditates cause they just keep you
will have these five problems and it's
interesting if there are five problems
you expect five solutions right yes this
problem most not sure that that's a
shame but there's eight solutions Mary
Cheney Voisin okay five problems it's
solutions
very famous okay and we just finished
the last hour we call 1919 means
experiential explanation of the problems
when she launched a tabula Shinya
problem and practical and we actually
did a meditation together for one hour
I didn't we tried to repeat the problems
in the actual meditation substance
immediate action so I have a suggestion
for Tim a CIA director Michael nice
proportionately t-midi wreck tracer in
the next hour for our Gold Club
broadcast the junior silver chalices
yeah primo if here at the national
called Koba
will be describing the problems from the
ancient book mobile my piece of the
problem is three Emily technique but I
suggest that we will send
down Mamiya can translate your estimate
Oh Maria morbid obesity there's a
one-hour meditation you can do I didn't
ask much details to go through the nine
stages of meditation and you go through
all the problems related to the same
David start immediately
it produced a problem oh and you learn
how to fix them your boot is nice
colorful his privates
so we'll be we'll be posting that unlike
in the next by tomorrow night all right
and we'll put it up online so you can
actually practice these problems and how
to fix them so today I'll just talk
about them but I encourage all the go
Club members yeah gene IDs of safely on
the gold COBOL do the actual meditation
who did what's the meditation we used
cocoon we did that so makes possible
Tomlin which is giving people comfort
taking away their problems the Yanni
illudium comforter is the bear Anya we
need problem who did we do that tongue
land on Nicole me do a little Glen on
yourself there's a special Tony you can
do
yes sob dumpling cuz their most ideals
if you have an important meeting if you
have to give a teaching this afternoon
it's very helpful in morning watching
Polly is the autumn weather Dean do the
tone line on yourself still on Glen is
some hours ago
in the afternoon and then the afternoon
me this afternoon will get a big
injection of energy from the morning me
back then what Nimoy yeah Buddhism
fellowship a groom
energy at Minya Kotori ultram do vegetal
sir
so in that one meditation online vietnam
is it that same line you can learn to do
this helping yourself later in the day
meditation the s'mores no chief mimosa
mimosa beer who do seem normal evasion
and at the same time you can experience
all the meditation problems that i'm
going to talk about three most types
problem so we're in the middle of an AC
i teacher training facility in Adrienne
good Lisa
the students here in Arizona at the
retreat center is this to us every treat
center which is completely fold this
week there's not any other place to stay
in the pose diss epona need a lenient
novice about no minister even all the
Bears and the wild pigs we asked them to
move out with McSweeney so I'm gonna
actually go through the actual homework
questions yeah but I did series both of
them are thereabouts and that way you
can finish your homework off about them
and I have exciting news for all the
russian-speaking audience listening oh
is that listening all still a closed
case it is a closure we are making plans
for a CI teacher training in Europe we
plan you don't a separate images to
label wrote them and there'll be a
Russian language music so purposely we
arranged for Russian woman to marry a
German guy by the home with Selena
travel in Arkansas elaborate ruse
creationist esq Cheney and they are
cooperating they got married here
actually
so we'll be starting those programs soon
it's Gordon with the program understand
okay so here we go first of the five
meditation problems the Tibetan word I
don't know everyone likes it around the
whole world say lay low lay low
it sounds like what it is what does it
mean lazy slob yeah okay our chamber
horse okay so it's very similar okay
so lay low means okay now listen when
you teach it this is a teacher training
right this not really don't call it
laziness nian is divisive Alenia okay
put on your second husband second way
accent is positive accent erosion a
second wife I don't feel like meditating
today yeah you choose to see what if
actually deteriorate
I didn't have a good sleep last night
young useful is watching I had a fight
with my husband yesterday
I'm very busy
oh my stomach a little bit upset then
the first meditation problem is making
excuses why you don't have to meditate
today Daniel movies and it sounds like
that I don't
yes II wouldn't if I to me I don't feel
like meditating today Jimmy did you ever
see what's the last sentence that mine
always says just before they go to
breakfast margarita - imperium coitus
after Koerner so gang got it so young
but tomorrow I would definitely minute
ok guys does it sound familiar
there are 4 solutions - yes a Malayalam
say depe timber solution Dibby Dibby the
mature oak a very famous ok that's why
you have 8 solutions to five problems
because the first problem has four
solutions of a problem material singing
the first problem has the has the three
extra solutions we have a problem is
three the politician
ok Peppa
ok Peppa in sanskrit is shredder
shudders Papa Rooskies nothing we're
hard SRD certain in English cardiac same
same rude
cardi CRD surd certain same as in
Russian and the words father comes from
theater shut up
so Russian is very close to which is
very cool
so Russian speakers you are super cool
it's easier for you to learn sounds good
sure it means faith faith okay you have
faith but special meaning of faith not
as so biznitch engineering okay and when
I explained the four solutions to the
first problem I like to talk about your
high school you know school okay and it
happened to me in high school some lost
corner you see a nice-looking girl in
school
remember our fiftieth anniversary anyway
how does it happen in high school first
dude you look at the girl
macho this model it's an idea order boy
she's pretty cool and in your mind
Mia you are making a list we system
later okay
Oh her hair is cool oh she's body so
cool yellow car I see her voice is so
cool cool and when she likes them is so
cool
so this is how you're supposed to think
about meditation don't do it oh okay
people who meditate they're so calm
they can focus their mind I knew what
was the focus you know it yeah always
smiling I need alibis they always wear
cowboy hat I need sit down lots of
cowboys coach level just kidding you
chew okay and they do better business
also
I knew business okay because they can
focus on on things for problem-solving
meditation is fantastic and for
controlling your emotions in your
business it LeConte rally of any emotion
business
meditation is incredible the businessman
or businesswoman who doesn't get upset
when the business has a problem will
become super cool business persons
businessman or businesswoman Catherine
near as travels activist Nikhil problem
of businesses a super Kruti businessman
a businesswoman on and much more wealthy
and you know it's not the goal of life
to collect money we just nick nick are
our teacher just had a baby a few days
ago right I was there I refused to come
in the room when the baby come out but
just after I come in the room so I I can
stay I'm sure that you come into this
life naked recorded Sapna's only me and
you go out of this life naked you don't
carry money and when it's time to go you
have to leave the money Ramiro to
achieve actually small separating and
you're naked but no if you have focused
yes no was focus you can be more
successful in this life and you can help
more people
meditation can help you become
financially successful and before you
leave naked if it is simple we do it so
that not only you can help more people
my diamond business boy I'll mostly
business I think a total we spent five
million dollars on saving the ancient
books five million u.s. dollar I didn't
ask Rania driven ethnic so it's useful
to make money and this broadcast is
being done for the gold club Russian
speakers in fear Qatari videos lately
and I'm called Clovis a pitch there from
Russia Ukraine Kazakhstan other
countries I see you crying because I
found it a druggie strap that's why I
put the Ukrainian and Russian national
colours on my script I see what you
little basket Oh crying skin and sauna
and a flop
yo ski and so those people listening to
this broadcast
luiz de cataluña fear they have a club
of over 1000 people know when you see a
lot of Ukrainian people they're all
donating at least $1.00
and if see any minute endure per month
cars the music and so far they have
raised more than $100,000 180 yeah
[Applause]
and John Brady over there we have the
same air conditioning NASA Tanaka we can
get Sonya and we spent together we spent
32 years treated vaca-oom of nice Usha
saving the ancient books
they have employed all the ancient books
from ancient India 4600 books is at
least Nico 3 of me easy in division of
computer they're online they're free I
need those appear online and we are
translating them ok and we are they
found they just found 300,000 books in
Mongolia and if told customers didn't
know what 3 statistic Mongolia and
Cristina kacica
and we also have some of our Sanskrit
experts here today so I have a very
strong international team sceneline it's
not okay come on then and because of the
Gold Club help me she called Koba they
can feed their kids where's your kid
I need small good karma okay so
of course we have to our staff works I
don't know like 90 hours a week Marcia
start reading care about the given hasta
to soft needs you know we pay them like
ten cents an hour
they sit scent of chess but it has even
the ten cent have to come from someplace
so we're very grateful and we have many
many refugees you know see some watching
Minogue isn't in India they are typing
the ancient books I new voice video and
we have a very cool project in Europe on
a C's class thing which is for the
refugees from countries like Syria
Afghanistan Iraq Syria Afghanistan and
they are learning a skill to support
themselves and their families
I believe there are one of the first
refugees in Europe to legally work on
their new skill which is sewing we teach
them how to use sewing machine the
agency cut really Ghana is a child
we brought they know we now look I knew
just the sheets they are using sewing
machine to make book covers for the
engine books and easily machine digital
services device
applause kissed cannula driven ethnic
and we are paying them in we and they
have to make three hundred thousand book
covers um doesn't it says that's 300
South trees the trees applause Trista T
sister okay and the director of that
project is here nor
can you come up here I thought you might
like to see where all that money's going
to see what she's doing here is our
Sanskrit Act expert Aisha and her three
- Aisha her son you're seen Kylie
because of your help were able to pair
stuff Thank You Kari his dad has another
project oh you've all pop with
recuperate where's his dad they got
permission from the government of Mexico
I need sugar as a senior private to
start training 23 million children my
chest was six three million of the tea
so the Congress has voted to support it
Congress there will be teaching kids to
drink healthy green drinks that always
alone in that big kid in the morning
each kid will get a great drink because
obesity childhood obesity - fat oh but
how much does it yes it has spread in
Mexico Mexico strenuous from the United
States is America so I think over 50% of
kids are overweight and they will get
they will get diabetes
they all have heart problems any fires a
problem a system they will die young we
already know their future and it spread
to China
American food candy candy Jim Bakker
20,000 shops in opened in China and they
are teaching kids to eat bad food yes
you do
I think there's a McDonald's in the
Kremlin near the Kremlin I saw it
teaching Russian kids to eat that which
is okay so this is very good for your
meditation
it's a Watterson okay eat well have a
green drink every morning cause the
woods alone and a people you don't need
to eat a big breakfast soy lattes after
and they will help your yoga I'm sorry
okay so first quality to fix lay low
yakisoba mochi is privately I don't feel
like meditating today yeah
think about how cool it's gonna be when
you learn too many to do I do my set on
car class and the budget cut down now
it's like admiring a girl in your high
school
about sights do scoffs :
then what's the second step in the high
school roof that was shocked Scalia you
have to decide I want that girl widow's
made you see yeah quite sure that your
school that's called dimbo it's the
second solution to laziness it of Tarawa
senior clean it's the second solution to
I don't feel like meditated but I've
devil a manatee tomorrow cynic problem
young chui's touch to her choice 20
minute
laughter besides Shakespeare said see if
tomorrow and tomorrow and tomorrow
creeps in this petty pace from day to
day to the last syllable of recorded
time it means your tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow okay so second solution edition
yeah I want it I want that girl who's
the girl good meditation oh wow
looks cool I can get rich I can get
peaceful I can help other people
oh my hope is about Gotham Spa coin them
I can help other people I want that yeah
okay that's a decision okay admire it
Abashidze and decide to get it a
petrosini positive okay then with the
girl in the high school that teams the
escapes :
there's a special system yes the subway
system so 100 years ago when I was in
high school we don't have online
anything we don't have computers so we
have to carry books each class has a
separate book and those books are heavy
and thick design it's an illusion of
Allah didn't know koneko nice it's Nikki
what she told it to Jolie
so you get a big test Arad notebook
tetrad big notebook for all your classes
one one to keep all your notes
then you have a big nose and you put
that you pile the books on it you walk
around the school like this it was cause
it seemed I could squash : okay now how
do you meet a girl
that you chose her and you want her
really Catherine you arranged to go
around the corner when she comes around
the corner and you bang tetrapods all
the books and then she won't get down
she was like then you have to say I'll
help you I hope you suppose here's your
boy do you want to go out with me on
Friday so the third solution is do
something do something
I can't work hard but it is work hard to
get militants but it is service to
approach it every day I don't care how
you feel you have no with Sebastian
if you feel good meditation if you feel
bad just do your meditation if you had a
good sleep
do your meditation if you had a bad
snake blocker spider
do your meditation if your body feels
great deal way she shuts the cloth do
your meditation if your bag hurts in
your leg hurts and it's time it hurts do
your goddamn you should do it
understand that's number three if you do
that you're gonna get the date you're
gonna get ah we buy goods in a civilian
at the jumpin
his restaurant on camera bag Avenue
opens Kirsten like a cool TV new was it
Japanese Mongolian ski even then I had a
scene even at that time I had a seat
from Manali Mongolian yeah and then if
you're so nice okay that first it's so
beautiful and that's the fourth
correction to laziness little yeah
because you work hard in your meditation
school kavoussi robotics famous that's
right you knocked down her books many
times then you get to go on the date
then you go to the garden it's sad and
it feels so nice Shin Jung Shi Jong Shin
Jang means your mind and your body are
really strong to meditate it does not
change the watch it cela a wash oh she
lived let me do that sir
you did your yoga the only yoga you
drank your green drink you you meditate
many times you suffer right Ichi Shoku
and then you get the result and when you
sit down to meditate
it's like someone giving you a massage
of your mind and your body that your
ideal like massage or myself
you sit down to meditate you're like a
pyramid
and the mind feels totally happy oh my
she shares a palmist okay that's the
fourth correction - I'll meditate
tomorrow it swarthy antidote we
have a problem because you want him
anything
you are making excuses to manatee like
in the afternoon you like maybe I could
just do a little bit more I mean I
finished my meditation this morning yeah
that quenches time you thought so Audra
I did a good hour for me this year and
it tells always doing there with yoga I
don't know I didn't reach this level yet
but in the afternoon he was he and John
Brady yesterday you sneak outside do
some more poses after that yoga class
you write poses I notify you again if
mrs. John embrace officially is shown
him no scope I do a yoga nasty ash just
zoo mashhad she she's real crazy yeah
okay so the fourth correction to
laziness then you get addicted to
meditation and that's a good addiction
we finished the first problem and we
finished the first problem solution
which has four parts okay tepid symbol
so well ginger ginger okay you you
admire that thing vomiting or to get it
you work hard to get it and spill their
books but we see that about it there's
still a couple cheats Rania a technique
yet and then you get the result is the
Mongolian dinner and afterwards
we apologize she's Carly resisted using
my words khmer surin ifs and you feel it
feels so good then you don't have that
problem anymore somebody says let's
meditate tomorrow I'm doing it today
Francis come on let's just melt it
tomorrow like why wait till tomorrow
let's do some extra attention does that
serve I see what you sure that's this
afternoon okay like that okay
all right second problem this is a
famous code word secret word it is my
secret as for Thamud Japanese I forgot
the instruction of my teacher that's the
second problem yes that will instruct
sis we were cheated after a problemo I
forgot my teachers meditation
suggestions for me that's it that's the
second problem problem but what it means
is you lost in your meditate during your
meditation you lost the object which
your teacher gave you so the one of the
first important things in meditation is
selecting your meditation object for
today
and that's why it's so important to have
a meditation teacher right we'll talk
wash them it's okay for me to pass and
they will give you a suggestion I know
you have important meeting today
yes nature so I suggest you meditate
tonglen on yourself in the afternoon but
0 is subordinate on Glenn my voice to be
a Buddhist so what's the meditation
object
Bobbi Expedia Dodson yeah my nervous
this afternoon me that yet
minotaurs at nearly yakitori buddhism
near nature and that's your meditation
object so you close your eyes you know
and you say okay my teacher gave me a
meditation I'm supposed to meditate
about my this South afternoon yeah
Kotori your Moodle and you focus on
Michael in the afternoon and after one
minute by magic look at em again it
changes into panchak punch in Russian :
Jerome yo John okay like here's Michael
Michael in the afternoon then suddenly
he changed to Russian donut those key
points you I got it
that's the second meditation problem
this afternoon Michael changed into a
Russian donut and you're not sending
Michael energy anymore you are planning
how to get a donut after meditation
Buddhism in there give a planner its
punching okay then you have to apply
this fifth correction which is the
correction to the second problem in fact
every minute tateshina cough thyroid
problem in Wisconsin and it's called
chamber September okay so in Arizona
where we are right now what is the
message has in this area all the Cowboys
grow cows that's why they call cowboy
see a cowboy meatiest cut off in the
fight
boy so they keep cars and actually they
let them go in the desert you know some
really cut post I'll buy these books
once a year they collect them I need
cigarettes okay the collection method is
very interesting methods for a cut off
which is insidious you get a big cow
truck you drive through the deserts flow
you have a big bag of carrot soup
Markovic and you go carrot and you throw
and then the cows that I can come to get
the carrots Co you can have a second
carrot just get in the truck it's kind
of stuff I watch him doing it there's
always wanted to cause very similar to
word if suggest Baraka of kateri pod
omnivore do when you ask them to do they
don't want to do then that cowboy
hesitate to have a rope Lhasa it's
colossal yeah and you throw it at the
car and it goes over their head and then
you it takes a lot of strength
now your mind is just like a wild cow
but Vova you are the cowboy that's why
it's important to meditate with your
cowboy hat on is the materials Cowboys
push nation when your mind goes to the
doughnut that point then you have to
catch him
by much pull it back even to this
afternoon's Michael Anna brodnik abierta
catimor Mike look at our Buddha
Shinyoung so the Tibetan word timber
timber it means pull that rope come back
here
Boucher sir you can I promise you you
can have a doughnut after many type
ramen I be sure we share posting it
that's the power just punch it
no green Jing for you honey I promise
you big doughnut I be SharePoint you
will make any toilet drink the green
drink and I told to drink the green then
you pull your mind back now I'll tell
you a meditation trick and I we talked
about it this money yes well but Kivar
you don't fight with your mind you will
lose
okay talk to your mind persuade your
mind
yeah donut is great is delicious and I
promise we'll eat one after meditation
so that's decided so you don't have to
think about anymore I don't like Yong
Yong goo I'm telling you the truth
you will get a donut after meditation
mostly meat that's it follow just punch
it so don't worry about it
don't forget we have a meeting this
afternoon is that one sec you know we
gotta get ready for this media let's get
back to it okay so talk to your mind
voice it doesn't work to fight
you have to persuade your mind if you
say don't think about honest don't think
about doughnuts once again nobody in the
world likes to be told what to do
nikto meeting a little bit condemned
coverage to your mind is just like that
don't get bossy with your mind you boots
you slip it up or something same MO
nobody likes it be be clever be a good
sounding oh hey oh I let's get one after
meditation decided so it is a lot okay
okay all right now you happy so it's
just yeah I'm happy
daya justice so what are we gonna do for
the next half hour let's just go back to
the meditation talk to your mind okay
all right so second solution which is
really the fifth solution to the second
problem okay bring your mind back what
was the second problem problemo
I lost the object I started thinking
about all right third problem say Tinga
Tinga by the way russian speakers don't
worry I will try to finish in the next
15 minutes maybe third problem it's
called sleepy mind and busy mind okay
third problem has two parts problem at
wilchester
sleepy mind and busy mind and leave
using a toy so you know I studied
meditation for 30 years on my teacher
and I lived with him in the same class
and I I told my one morning I told it he
said how's your meditation I don't know
I always get sleepy I told these guys
one day even I fell asleep I hit my head
on the wall miss to collapse I came to
breakfast with my teacher I have a big
bump on my head
he's very smart he's gassy Kashi Kashi
Superga she want the Queenie prestigio
soo progressions say ah looks like you
got sleepy problem number three you hit
your head on the wall right yeah he said
why you get so sleepy I said well I
didn't get my sleep last night you made
me fix the you know sidewalk I didn't
get my sleep last night then he said
every meditator needs to sleep well -
have a good meditation cars don't
practical me that's amused Maharashtra
was the passage that we made for ocean
Mindy dancing then I remember I asked
him can you teach me deep secret tantric
method not to sleep I am the worst in
Abu cheats secret no more glue book
almost possible in his fights he said no
he's the very famous answer to all my
questions
he hurt his throat in car accident
before I met him she loved he talks just
like Star Wars all the time don't ask me
for the secret method
I mean I said me method they're all
people have to sleep
even the big Lamas have to sleep if you
don't want to be sleepy in your
meditation try sleeping on your bed my
son Lee wisdom is not superpowers
so how to fix the third problem well
partly should get enough sleep don't eat
before meditation near your stupid me
that green drink is fantastic it will
give you energy during your meditation
you polish the more energy of every time
you look at me so you know but don't eat
food before meditation only yes see you
do period missing you the sleepy okay
the other problem 3b the second part of
the third problem is your mind is too
busy problem is to wash all solutions in
the toy it was mainly your mind wants to
think about what you have to do this
after this today
it's trying to think about what you have
to do today okay stove on but it's ty
you d like to change and again my
suggestion is don't try to block it like
you know it don't yell at your mind
nobody likes to be stop thinking about
what we have to do today I'm still I'm
certainly but then your mind will just
think more things you have to do
okay so learn to talk to your mind as
you should talk to your children know
Jesus go but it's the same imam Cox's I
mean it's me
because the mind that doesn't meditate
is very similar to
a bad kid that most Katarina coaches
make it serious but doesn't pluck
American Co oh I mean you're gonna do
this in this in this in this just after
your meditation after humanity pause
let's focus on the okay so don't fight
with your mind you will lose we
progressed top tier mine yeah let's
let's think about it after meditation
you know we will stay in the meditation
seat and we will have a special post
meditation meditation about other things
we have to do today posting its own
absurd iniative Stoller's now let's go
back to our meditation okay so now the
classic solution for problem number
three yeah problem in our dream it's
called the smoke alarm yeah so we have
this special machines when there's smoke
in the room the the the machine
whenever Veronica enchiladas so you you
gotta have a mental smoke alarm means
dilated so you should install one now
I did promise each other okay and that
smoke alarm goes off it watches the
month that's what happened to me and
John pretty sure number 18 we meditate a
lot theorem we put the smoke alarm up
here we use it a lot it overheated
that's how you can tell the great
meditator that smoke alarm has two jobs
Oh a detector they mean is clear about
it if I get sleepy yes yeah let you know
as a surprise if I start thinking about
all the things I have to do today
yes and I do miss it we shall come you
know this one is do then the smoke alarm
goes Danger Danger PPP Danger Danger
[Music]
then there's some other subjects we we
can study later about subtle dumbest and
obvious et mr. Abu Musa said proud tone
cool some limits we're gonna go to
problem number four say do me
chiba-chiba do me cheaper do Nietzsche
so if you're married you know about
smoke alarms yes the vision Apple is
Amazon with night to protect erythema
smoke alarm in your house never go off
during the day always go up when you're
sleeping human is about with no map see
dust Rabat wait cut away
I believe it I think they put something
in the factory they put some clock
inside when the battery gets low and it
goes peep
you know that pretty beep every 20
seconds the most irritating sound for
sleep which exists happening you have
the berry Garlow and it goes beep then
you're like you know did you hear
something
you both wanted to know yeah let's go
back to sleep that's just a baby then
there's this fight you know husband wife
fight who's gonna put the battery in
this mope I just need that equal listen
I have important meeting tomorrow I need
to sleep that means you put Barry you
know right now what's the most stupid
thing you can both do at that moment ok
Sam I go polish cut the most results
with money on nobody takes
responsibility uniqueness about business
let's just go back to bed
we'll fix it in the morning all right
that's do me cheaper it do me cheaper
we'll fix it later then you both have
bad sleep all night
I mean if it goes that's okay but this
beep beep so the worst thing you can do
is just remember for
don't take action when you have to take
action we need that's problem number
four guess what's the solution oh god I
think our coalition
so homework question 4 is very easy
somebody has to get out of bed and put a
battery in the smoker and somebody has
to go into the mind and tell their mind
to shut up in a nice way don't be sleepy
don't think about donuts one chicken
that's why that teaches that don't think
about monkeys okay so that one's easy
okay now we're almost finished
and again we're giving this special
class just for you Gold Club people
because you are so cool in the whole
world you are the best Organization for
fundraising ACIP thank you any more yeah
be safe with us I did it Sam across
Natalie that's a meet across the border
and thank you too Maria and her husband
Peter thank you for organizing it's a
lot of work and we're very grateful my
CDs are valid a Mogan about this
possible and we are actually using the
books which you save you know something
negative is positive so we can go deeper
and deeper if we have more books and
they have covers okay now the last
problem number five it's very cool
so when I started in our diamond
business business we had only three
people and we have a tiny little office
with one small table Mikra office
against alone
we had three diamonds on diamonds we
tried to sell one then next day still
three times later we do we process
300,000 diamonds every day probabilities
that this is a mass of cars dating and
we became the one of the largest jewelry
companies and it was the largest time
Joey company in the world
it's a blossom a group known as the
companion of meeting what's the secret
meditation we know the five problems we
know the eight solutions and we used
them okay all day long okay we are
meditating on the mind is focus okay
problem number five you are very lucky
if you get it probably monomer PES mom
oh she will be obviously within your the
Barossa see why i talk about the diamond
company
which reminds me we had a big factory
why should we make 30,000 rings every
day we found out later every woman
average every woman in America has five
of our rings my part almost knowledge
top stratum cars the Americans causation
is actually one lady has ten one lady
doesn't have any you know but average
every woman in America has five of our
changed my Medicaid then the fact is
very big you know and the factory
manager was a very funny guy his name's
Kenny Lautman he's from New York
he taught from New York what is New York
a was that Kenny Lautman but maybe I'll
get in trouble till New York people they
talk like that
you're kyani what that regardeth maybe
you know someone who talks like that
they don't say coffee this is quality
you want some quality I need so much
coffee
why am I talking about that which my
why do the factory manager the
fact we men is a vote deserve what
mechanics that vote done
he always say listen geeky Michael if it
ain't broken don't fix it yes follow me
Chobani
okay very famous factory manager it
looks like that machines making noise
you know if it ain't broken don't fix it
yes the Islam Allah nice Revelator
in English we say don't mess with it man
Liscomb aquarium in the Narrows come
no new am I don't try to fix it
this planet okay leave it if it breaks
fixing yes llamas but it is yes what's
problem number five
okay problem on the merits you tried to
interfere with the meditation when it's
already going well
we put deities is prevalent mediate
Otsuka tree eat tacos refresh order now
you guys are not gonna have this problem
but just in case in the future
this year the meditation is going very
smooth tell the smoke alarm
take the battery out of the smoke alarm
okay don't do not check the meditation
when the meditation is flowing let the
meditation so what's solution number
fire question you better say it now say
it with a New York accent if it ain't
broke don't fix it okay so that
concludes our special Gold Club
meditation teaching there's lots more
you can learn you can learn to be a
meditation teacher with Tim and the
other Sigma other assistants see he is a
tricky case I with the help of Peter and
Maria Palmer should be primary they will
bring teacher training to Europe I need
and we look forward to you this year the
same rope a proper little crane in it to
karate
okay this year due out this year okay so
all right in the meantime you you cannot
teach meditation unless you are
meditating
don't try to fake it the student can
smell you teach the five problems very
nice solution very nice but you're
nervous unpleasant person then the
student is like Dharma Quixote
they have logic they are teaching
meditation they are nervous and they get
upset easily oh and you checked me
that's an in your digital cost reverses
therefore they are not meditating so you
can start your meditation teacher
training today
I don't watch that soon I check the boy
dreams delirium and do your meditation
okay thank you for listening
[Applause]
the immediate now is the Varni Couture
but sake was still stop Russo area she
sang GU spanning over a she group with
boulevards premise T theory nerves yet
even fight over your notes examining
Dhamma he produces Tommy amassed and a
village is just an actress the Muslims
of Daniel Ameerpet yes my prosthetic
adorably
he only three Vida
six arts and reacting quickly with Kabir
- no not rio grande por una dama go very
well but soon we were in a film on the
pyramid motion globe would tow
magnetically the french poet but salute
feel me
nature's notches sonic
nemanja now beautiful hija teaches boys
away the closeness lo emerge to go over
it is possible fix odds we fix zero it
is not built we could she keep the
commandments we did Bob wave fill me
with motor diffident with material with
motio to me you might not need that
needed of a moment ago the Prescotts
tennis portfolio
in nature's large waves quality freedom
there is more treaty freedom but also
soldier exaction exerts as shortcuts to
traffic supreme authority provided by
Sonia wake up by guillotine a biack
knowing nice nice it was not a such as
much it you idiot no nice in the whites
cousins now not much chance to watch it
what what are the nature nature without
the soldier senior you watching 308
large excuse it a crocodile pressed a
nap at Siloam never got off but salawats
at Awad vase feel him we filming down
another white and nature
yeah what's material cilantro but I'm
searching and appreciates tapas Lavazza
a popcorns image ads in imagine if what
stand up but Zulu if CPD studies popcorn
sirs three or mean if exception
seriousness law when the best come dr.
Hatake visit upon meeting the atop Aloha
it much it cut the class Nizam sir and
those nitrogen bridge alone a stylist
Briana Hanabusa grenades way Astra to
the Moscow style
sure we position Cyrano styler Ostrom
Edgar it does magic art
i'ma goin with that the waiter when I
release my yeast washing mediator said
sure
he watched me do cottonseed a stock of
all stray it was decidedly go if you're
cold moment filled me but well dreamiest
and spud saloon with that and otherwise
uh you know unique appetite news ideas
ideas go Connecticut and you got a
Picasso with fish but solely any sniper
to my sequentially demerged Anya
Ameerpet each Kurosawa pros that my son
uses Kotori ever machine Adamas was
sunny with my abide term but nobody'll
asleep after it is sent to pop boots
went astray any which was a stray away
English coast a little savonia was the
god of straying and we must post I love
with this build so a nice yellow
it wasn't the intercooler Kabuto was
Whitaker Stovall yes three Mia tada
bring up Simon stop of your good foot
was Bush Dean rather swash Nick Mingo
yes a balloon a periodic stick emerged
for probity Peru is miserable the period
eaten after Roy is the erroneous
reported purified agenda treaties in his
revolted
proceeded Java easier stable show this
year
Nami redeem it numerous got posted to
focus it out
Nathan action him not open yet sir
nearby ie
near achieve what crystal soccer
mcchrystal pracinabarhi garage Nakuru
new garage name when I met you
straighten epitope eat away by message
to it
prose brush Nina with such a lecherous
Josh for photons
such a cheat embrace the technology
booboo GPD pretty with as I was by me to
study near patrol each toy ten years
media Dodson though wasn't corrosion he
did that because he cares a great video
to some Johnson common separate Hiroshi
Carson's prisoner whole carnage it
becomes its residual it in the premiere
priests circle crystal exact are oh yeah
goes not this do it at the pro style is
been eating GB it upon the rabbits
[Music]
- no idea program Drago
you
yes the universe singing oh yeah boy
series on it watch it
yeah my yeah my dinky crystal exact rit
period selling mmm yes i you know
approach of agora various yeah yeah yeah
video very overtures Cavazos Mars what's
wrong
Martha Virginia that should be a puzzle
would sign you pity
it doesn't match it which in today's
only me terrible I'm also better
individual yes
Brooke wash oh boy she convinced me he
was Mitch nightosphere item hooray in
that way Monica crystal is Sakura evil
bacteria material was dime amount and
Diggy Schmeichel yanostamos Ichiko
Seichi of battery
yes time uppity really was booing
shushing yeah let that way my sister
could have a father I see but crisp Alex
ahora me the question you stuck to the
Palazzo Meenakshi
chai is this is this is Russ on Lee was
here I met him at the Sheraton is did
Avakian I didn't even know me as a
teacher
yes you was some livers appear was
supposed to pop probably yet the caused
by shock of horror yama go serious
Mercutio's crime Eric I mean upon
midnight base for mainly Spearin yes
certain years Robert a it then think of
something inspiring to you but do me
jump - Tova's - normally I'd was my girl
wearing a conductor was Cavalli low
vision
no classy jiske premier a space honest
Adam but do much so sure now say yes you
bring me enjoy this would store wait
wait I didn't is Kalki I did instead of
middle of stroke monopoly we I did not
okay toka voice karma Boyd's dings yes
service if I choose to it's taking my
vitals we're taking my lincom europa
titus that me about me i'm and you go to
some of the USDF you feel is if we
choose to be of Aloha
that was a nice easy way mush cough
novel only issue versus mister yeah try
to anemia with a posting the Jimmy stop
really she was the Pope in Australia he
was with ninotchka gruesome sevilla me
de Bracy know what the period deep
freeze you it was Prosecco harness
training when you choose to severe so
business when you do much Diamond
Mountain also been a mister we don't
notice a change Petraeus tokati
ambassador Priya an issue Bosnia and
observe a 10-year sport serious Etta's
bore the Austria and you go ahead but do
mighty coefficients to visit ecosystems
I with some wasabi Nikolaevich is
roughly on Afridi he washed your body
wash with your disposition this is GC
Washington
he said this is Justine you a new CEO
was this an if she are aborted in wood
products a vision is that if it is easy
to see see see some ID so you've made an
about was it's rock it was more
especially expecting and then he was
morally still in Islam is a true way my
dealings to Mars across trainee at the
brilliant II called so one at Anita your
tidy computer over noon approached us
Sadie need called sauce brilliant ensues
llamas ceviche sinister una llamada was
pretty started shifting thirst away
stitches really adapt at the media and
Judah you know a third Oconee pradosham
it in the OT Nia Bush numbers the Romans
he Priya hurt Sudha them amount if we
identity throat sure yes yes become what
you just got a facade but there's many
figures can do more good distances
vitamin with aqueous or vitamin ultram
my privilege Enya Adam is urban areas
just as easy as margosa boots of the
occlusion
so that we in Civitas zoom which the way
I did is dissimilar
Kotaro special Pravda we cut it which is
stable
Ojeda topology touch the work attitude
pollito strategy edited the boots and
receive booster booster nam
Nagaraju the Cobras who did she talk the
over City pizza this is GT roboted we
pay Thomas just with there's legitimate
the oceans a phenomenon when you do my
test over soybean or we also been a yet
visual the visual card of a cs9 we are
solving a well I didn't is I didn't is
certainly million of meeting well show
me over I didn't study non cars like
this the meaty which new Luigi no when
you provide Yamaguchi visual coast of us
toast of whiffs
dv/dt ICBM cars each other exist where
ideal is time you know one but do mighty
of item cockney boot but do we
practically melee only edge too much the
opposite
oh yes or no star you push we need of
Darwin evolution but how it is a douche
a tentative us proceed being knighted
mechanic for it no way do sure there's
no stamina and the ricotta cheese dollar
oh wait oh boy Pamunkey waiting I should
do sure if she was person Darwinism not
a problem over a at Sidhu
Matthias audience it is your way of
solving process not do much but that's
who they are visual
yeah visual version written you know
visual was of our personalities
yes there's a nice robot it yes score
upon wish me to score upon machine it
produces no it's a metaphor upon machine
one rosary sure it's a pure white
version media taut so easy of I'm not
the one resolution I probably would stop
immediate action yet emitted at a duck
it is a duck asana Sutra Sutra Jean if
she was of simple Paco eg Roger Stanton
it praises he did Naraku miss edita CdTe
periodic accordion pre-written digital
CD t propagates the mostest AMA whooshes
those moderate is it Skouras chorus
Cornish method you was business
covariant regularities but it is a serum
with April on each team responds in
threes but Nimet is proculus is now
bully of a sock Bulova Socony hasta put
up when you see it in IVF but it is
never shown over it past maternity wards
was not written across name is but move
it which is it so it is not quality with
a missus it has some as the need
additional problem i vibrate media tots
pan yachts and I will never should know
you a Telugu but is never certain
Anna was a homo it was material group
who to the watchman he thought sorry
Pezzini ago I do I comfortable with
Bruce much what this even on its own my
own dough Miki get you what you need you
because they bring in my bring your
mother's wombs rasoi shades on price nya
yeah is named opal his la managed I had
praised nice it's occurred that they
followed me to screen image in sniper to
move Postini vada Takaya Cullinan you
Magoo a teppanyaki is 3 meter history
method that was proposed which discuss
out was a wig loop which the problem was
really mediate that matter as the minute
the some ways the minute II at Australia
it was me that the cat dragged in me do
that Tony booty Bratton destroyed us it
was so much new Christine is moderately
least I do my chambers and would
away - mr. Italy so let me that I
didn't know what a shitty mediator is
positing here but dv/dt focus at touch
network when a channel team needed at
sea and the dutch name the shirts
mr. verse two issues dish comes on it
should meet blah blah blah blah famous
he searches the mini solution Nash
Nietzsche breaches that piece of
initiatives physically G Kotori butter
first night she told me that way mama
Loretta Boyd corrode his pizza cut away
they ain't my waters that the Butley
nice piece I suppose the well a team is
what you had no I did edit Rita yeah me
both tele there's peace Fuji Kotori
Ashley that there is no the annual staff
to would forage in a shoe preaches that
if broke mom's whiskey stylist total of
it and buy the more booze my edema no
way a starry starry lady I'm not gonna
sue my snowcone England if ya pass
leading a group immediate Otto past
matryona was when appointed super both
immediate thoughts assaulted me was was
night energy be it was night drove over
video tag genius if gene even emergency
the witch Museum
what up E yes yet Natasha Natasha
national zoomit just need to give a sh
Picard summary to drink a program
Picasso morning my du Chocolat Nevada
nada it's been mostly upon you
when you're adopted that hated me that
uh spoke avoid washroom
that reads all knowledge ladyship that's
why Yoda highness telling me that the
thing positive periods of scholar the
Dharma gt80
roasted status for the continuity
it's the shade